<resources>
    <string name="app_name">INC Playlist</string>
    <string name="version_number">v 1.01</string>
    <string name="all_songs">All Songs</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">

        <center><b>IGLESIA NI CRISTO (Church of Christ) MUSIC APP \n
Terms of Use</b></center>
\n
\n
I.	<b>INTRODUTION</b>
\n
This document (the “Terms”) sets out the terms and conditions governing visits, access and use of the music service INC MUSIC APP by you.

The “Services” means the music service branded ‘INC MUSIC APP’, mobile and device applications and all services provided by the INC, INC’s affiliated entities or other third parties with whom INC contracts to provide the Services that are inherently related to this music service. These may include but are not limited to websites and applications for desktops, tablets and mobile handsets.

The Services are provided by the IGLESIA NI CRISTO, based on AUSTRALIA.
\n
        \n
        II.	<b>APPLICABLE JURISDICTION</b>
\n
        \n
The use of this service, and the entirety of this agreement, is bound by the statutory and contractual law on AUSTRALIA.
\n
        \n
        III.	<b>PRIVACY AND COLLECTION OF DATA ON LISTENING BEHAVIOUR</b>
\n
        \n
When you use the Services, we keep track of your listening activity, including the number and titles of songs to which you have listened, the songs, albums, or artists that you like or dislike, the songs you skip, and how frequently and for how long you listen to the albums.

We do this for a variety of reasons, such as to gain an understanding of the types of music, content, or features you and/or other similar listeners tend to like or dislike, and to improve the Services generally, which includes enhancing our music selection algorithms in an effort to provide you and other listeners with the music most suited to your tastes.

As this data is essential to the function of the Services, you may not opt out of our collection and use of such data or information. By accessing or otherwise using any portion of the Services, you hereby consent to the foregoing collection and use of your listening activity and behavior for the purposes set forth above
\n\n
        IV.	<b>AMENDMENTS AND CHANGES TO TERMS AND CONDITIONS</b>
\n\n
The current Agreement will appear on our website and/or the app with the effective date that the Terms were updated. INC may, in its absolute discretion, make changes to the Agreement. When we make material changes to the Agreement, we’ll provide you with prominent notice as appropriate under the circumstances, e.g., by sending you an email.

Your continued use of the Services after the changes have been made will constitute your acceptance of the changes. Please therefore make sure you read any such notice carefully. If you do not wish to continue using the Services under the new version of the Agreement, you may terminate the Agreement by contacting us at legal@iglesianicristo.org.

\n\n
V.	<b>LICENSE TO USE</b>
\n\n
Subject to the terms and conditions of this Agreement, INC hereby grants to you a limited, revocable, non-exclusive, non-transferable, non-sublicensable license to access the Services, and otherwise view and use the Services to the extent permitted by its intended functionality, for your own individual personal, non-commercial purposes and not for the sublicense to or use by third parties.

You may only access and/or use the Services through the certified applications or intended methods that INC makes available to you. Any other use not authorized herein, or by INC in writing, is strictly prohibited and a violation of this Agreement. INC may revoke and/or terminate the foregoing license with respect to any aspect of the Services at any time, for any or no reason.
\n\n
VI.	<b>PROHIBITED/RESTRICTED USE</b>
\n\n
The Services contain content, such as sound recordings, audiovisual works, other video or audio works, clips, images, graphics, text, software, works of authorship, files, documents, applications, artwork, trademarks, trade names, metadata, album titles, sound recording titles, artist names, intellectual property, or materials relating thereto or any other materials, and their selection, coordination and arrangement (collectively, the “Service Content”). The Service Content is the property of the INC and is protected by copyright. The Service Content is made available to you only for your personal use as expressly permitted under these Terms.

You are prohibited from using the Service Content as follows:
\n\n
•	Except as permitted under the Terms, all copying, distribution or other use of the Service Content is prohibited without the prior written consent of the Service Content rights holders.
•	You have no right to engage in the commercial use, sale, resale, assignment, license, modification, making of copies or derivative versions, display, distribution or promotion of the Service Content.
•	You have no right to play or perform any of the Service Content in public.
•	The use or posting of the Service Content on any other website, application or otherwise, or sharing of the Service Content in a networked computer environment, for any purpose is expressly prohibited.

\n\n
VII.	<b>CONSENT TO COMMUNICATE</b>
\n\n
From time to time we may send you communications to the email address associated with your account. These communications may include, but are not limited to new songs, albums, and events that are near you.

By accepting this Agreement and using the Services, you expressly consent to the receipt of all such communications from or on behalf of INC. You may modify your email at any time within the Settings section of our website or applications. You may not opt-out of receiving account-related or transactional communications.


\n\n
VIII.	<b>IP OWNERSHIP</b>
\n\n
As between you and the INC, you acknowledge that INC retains all rights, title, and interest in and to all copyrights, trademarks, trade secrets, patents, and any other proprietary rights in the Services, the software and application programming interfaces (APIs) comprising the Services, and all content therein.

The Services are owned and/or licensed by INC and are protected by the laws of AUSTRALIA  and other countries in which the Services are made available. You agree to prevent any unauthorized copying, use, or distribution of the Services. Except as expressly provided herein, INC does not grant any express or implied right to you under any INC-owned or licensed copyrights, trademarks, trade secrets, patents, or other proprietary rights.
\n\n
IX.	<b>LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY AND INDEMNITY</b>
\n\n
You agree to defend, hold harmless, and indemnify us from and against all third party claims and all liabilities, assessments, losses, costs, or damages resulting from or arising out of (a) your alleged or actual breach of this Agreement, including your express representations and warranties; (b) your use or misuse of the Services; and © your alleged or actual infringement or violation of the rights of a third party, including without limitation any intellectual property rights, rights of publicity, and rights of privacy.
\n\n
X.	<b>ARBITRATION</b>
        \n\n
Any claims by INC, or claims by you arising out of, relating to, or connected with this Agreement must be asserted individually in binding arbitration administered by the Australian Disputes Centre in accordance with the prevailing contractual and administrative laws of Australia.
Judgment on the award rendered by the arbitrator may be entered in any court of competent jurisdiction. In addition to and notwithstanding the terms stated above, the following will apply to your disputes: (1) the arbitrator, and not any federal, state, or local court or agency, will have exclusive authority to resolve any dispute relating to the interpretation, applicability, enforceability, or formation of this Agreement including any claim that all or any part of this Agreement is void or voidable; (2) the arbitrator will not have the power to conduct any form of class or collective arbitration, nor join or consolidate claims by or for individuals; and (3) you hereby irrevocably waive any right you may have to a court trial (other than small claims court) or to serve as a representative, as a private attorney general, or in any other representative capacity, or to participate as a member of a class of claimants, in any lawsuit, arbitration, or other proceeding against us or related third parties arising out of, relating to, or connected with this Agreement.
The arbitration proceeding and the results thereof will be kept confidential by each party and not used for any purpose other than a party exercising its rights and fulfilling its obligations with respect to the other party; provided, however that either party may disclose the existence and results of the proceeding: (1) as required by law, rule, or regulation; (2) to its accountants, solicitors, and other fiduciaries.
\n\n
XI.	<b>TERMINATION</b>
\n\n
Subject to the terms of this section, this Agreement will remain in effect for as long as you use the Services. You may cancel your account and terminate this Agreement at any time and for any reason by following the instructions in the application.

We may terminate this Agreement and your access to the Services at any time and for any reason by providing notice to the email address you provided us. Upon any termination of this Agreement, the rights and licenses granted to you hereunder, including your ability to access and use the Services, will immediately terminate, and you shall immediately cease using any and all materials and other similar content in your possession or control that are proprietary to INC. You agree that we will have no liability to you for any costs, losses, damages, or liabilities arising out of or related to the termination of this Agreement. Any provision of this Agreement that should, by its nature, survive termination of this Agreement will survive its termination.

You also give us consent to delete all of the INC Music App Content that has been downloaded on your local or mobile devices.
</string>
</resources>